# **Siddharth Milind Konduru**

6 Candeltree Dr, #3 • Springfield, IL 62704

CELL PHONE [217-761-6199] • sid.konduru@gmail.com

#### **SUMMARY**

B.S in Electronic and Communication and with 1-year experience at Amazon.com, Inc. as a business process analyst. Currently an MIS graduate student, flexible problem solver with excellent attention to detail. Can easily assimilate in both individual and team work settings.

#### **EDUCATION**

### University of Illinois, Springfield, IL

May 2016

Master of Science in Management Information Systems

## Institute of Aeronautical Engineering, Hyderabad, Andhra Pradesh

May 2012

Bachelor of Electronic and Communication Engineering

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Technologies: C#, SQL, SAS, R-For Analytics.
- Databases: SQL Server, MySQL
- Web Technologies: ASP.Net, HTML, CSS, AngularJS, NodeJS, ReactJS, Java Script.
- Others: MS Excel, Functional Testing, Use Case Modelling, Statistical modelling, data analytics, UML, Text Mining.
- Certifications: IT Project Management, Business Process Management.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE / INTERNSHIP

# University of Illinois, Springfield, Springfield, IL

July 2015 - May 2016

Graduate Student Hourly

- Manage upgrades of department web page.
- Research, design and lead program offerings.
- Organize people and initiatives.
- Conduct program events and trainings.
- Photograph and design program graphics and media

### Amazon.com,Inc Hyderabad, Andhra Pradesh

June 2013 - June 2014

Business Process Developer/Customer Service Associate

- Communicated with Aces team in KAI-ZEN projects to improve and streamline business processes at Amazon.
- Responsible for assessing employers' performance and provide feedback.
- Evaluated change requests of the various policy administration systems and created knowledge transfer documents.
- Participated in daily requirements gathering sessions.
- Actively participated in defect management using Quality Center.
- Responded to customers' e-mails and answered queries regarding the orders placed.

#### Mag Web Technologies Hyderabad, Andhra Pradesh

September 2012 - April 2013

Project Trainee

- Worked with ASP.Net and C# back end SQL Server in MAG Web Technologies as a project trainee.
- Developed a program using ASP.Net and C# programming with back end as SQL Server as part of RMI (CMS) Project.

### SCHOOL ACTIVITIES / INTERESTS

- Founder and President of TARA meditation club
- Chief graphic designer of Asian Student Organization (ASO)
- Co-Chair of UIS It's On US, White House Bystander Intervention Campaign.